<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[I Code It | Juntao Qiu]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[I Code It is focusing on maintainable React code and masterful use of frontend technologies like Refactoring and Test-Driven Development.]]></description>
        <link>https://icodeit.com.au</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 22:59:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://icodeit.com.au/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interview with Packt on my new book React Anti-Patterns]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[As an application grows and more code is added, the initial loading time can become noticeably longer. This delay, sometimes lasting several seconds, can frustrate users. To avoid this, it's essential to optimize loading times.]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/interview-with-packt</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/interview-with-packt</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementing Dynamic Import and Code Splitting]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[As an application grows and more code is added, the initial loading time can become noticeably longer. This delay, sometimes lasting several seconds, can frustrate users. To avoid this, it's essential to optimize loading times.]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/dynamic-import</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/dynamic-import</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 04:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Headless Component: a pattern for composing React UIs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[As React UI controls become more sophisticated, complex logic can get intertwined with the visual representation. This makes it hard to reason about the behavior of the component, hard to test it, and necessary to build similar components that need a different look. A Headless Component extracts all non-visual logic and state management, separating the brain of a component from its looks.]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/headless-component-pattern</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/headless-component-pattern</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Web UI Development Is So Hard?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The landscape of web UI development is fraught with challenges that extend beyond writing code and designing interfaces. The inherent language limitations, nuanced data management, async complexities, and often-ignored unhappy paths collectively make this a formidable field. Architectural decisions ...]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/why-ui-is-so-hard</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/why-ui-is-so-hard</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 20:40:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The 2nd Editor of Test-Driven Development With React]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[After several months of revising and editiong and rewording, finally "Test-Driven Development with React and TypeScript," is officially out!]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/the-2nd-edition-of-atdd</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/the-2nd-edition-of-atdd</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 06:09:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modularizing React Applications with Established UI Patterns]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Established UI patterns are often underutilized in the frontend development world, despite their proven effectiveness in solving complex problems in UI design. This article explores the application of established UI building patterns to the React world, with a refactoring journey code example to showcase the benefits. The emphasis is placed on how layering architecture can help organize the React application for improved responsiveness and future changes.]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/modularizing-react-apps</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/modularizing-react-apps</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 04:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Test-Driven Development Mini Course]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Mini-Course on React and Test-Driven Development will provide you with the skills and knowledge to build robust, scalable and maintainable React applications.]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/tdd-mini-course</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/tdd-mini-course</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 06:09:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[React Clean Code -  mocking network scenarios]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Handling network requests is complicated. There are too many cases you have to consider on top of the asynchronised process. And testing these code can be even more challenging...]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/react-clean-code-network-mocking</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/react-clean-code-network-mocking</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 04:17:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Pragmatic Guide for React Network Programming]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Fetching data from a remote server can be challenging, especially when you have to consider cache, re-fetch, error handling, timeout etc...]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/the-pragmatic-guide-for-react-network-programming</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/the-pragmatic-guide-for-react-network-programming</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 10:52:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[If I Could Only Teach One Thing to a Beginner Developer]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, I got an interesting idea when I was writing a blog post about how to abstract your code to make it easier to reuse. I wanted to know what other developers think is the most important principle they would teach a newbie developer and why they would choose that design principle.]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/if-i-could-only-teach-one-thing-to-a-beginner-developer</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/if-i-could-only-teach-one-thing-to-a-beginner-developer</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 04:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementing Design System]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[So it’s not a single standard of how you would design at scale but a set of standards, and it is a visual language, which is important both by the user experience design and implementation...]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/implementing-design-system</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/implementing-design-system</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 06:15:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A story: from idea to product]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[As the saying goes: all great things have small beginnings. Even the most complicated product starts with a small and simple idea. And during the process of implementing it, even for a simple App like To Buy, there are many details to consider and polish.]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/idea-to-product</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/idea-to-product</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Different Levels of Abstraction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The ability of abstracting should be the most fundamental skill a developer should have, and I can't emphasise this enough. By abstracting, we can escape from the overwhelming seemingly irrelevant details to a solution that could solve all the problems at one go.]]></description>
            <link>https://icodeit.com.au/posts/levels-of-abs</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://icodeit.com.au/posts/levels-of-abs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 12:11:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>